[{"answer": "Well, I just put one foot in front of the other and keep it moving.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "How on earth do you do so much?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Oh my goodness.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Put family aside for one moment, professionally, if I could offer you the chance to just do one of those things everyday?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "I think that's been my curse, that I can't really find that one thing that keeps me content and happy.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "What do you think is the one thing you love most?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Music.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Right, but what about professionally?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Very hard.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "What was it like for you growing up in a single parent household?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "We didn't have a lot of money.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "No money, really?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "MITH: Yes, probably even more so.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Is she as kick-ass as you are?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "I think the endurance.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "What did she teach you, your mother, in terms of value, do you think?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "From my father and, you know, having been raised by a young mother who was really trying to find her way as well as having a little girl by her side.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "From your father?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "I would say that before he passed, we had an opportunity to find common ground.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Did he get better as he got older?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I forgive him now.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Did you forgive him?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "My creative mind.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "ORGAN: What do you think you get from him in terms of your personality?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "I think she's amazed, you know, and it doesn't stop.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "And for your mother, I mean, what does she make of this, absurd way that your life has turned since those early days?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "She worries when I work too hard.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Does she worry about you?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: (SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Hello?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "I'll make this meeting with Morrisey quick.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "You sure you got the right number?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "No, what's mine is yours.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Well you just make sure you keep my side of the bed warm, OK?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "I mean, it all happens on that show, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "He --", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What does the other man in your life, the one sitting opposite you right now, what does he make of all that?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Yes, he does and I think it --", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "He produces it with you, right?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "I can.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Can you watch him do it?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "When we come back.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Are you going to ask me when we come back?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I would say that's pretty much on the nose.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Much more than people might think?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "You didn't make it easy, did you?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I would say Will came at a time in my life where he saw beauty in me that I didn't see in myself at the time.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Well, what made you fall in love with him?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "I mean, we make love in some interesting places.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "It can be at times but it's not like a crushing fault, but you said, one thing and I gave you one.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Is that a fault?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "MITH: No, we don't scream at each other.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Do you ever scream at each other?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Both of us.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Who's the boss?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "It's interesting because when I think about the pressures that I had growing up, you know, living in a drug infested neighborhood.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Do you ever get concerned about having kids go down your route so young?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "And when I see these young people, we often get criticized for encouraging them to be stars, but when you hear a Jackie Evancho or someone who is so incredibly gifted, and my first question is, show me the parents?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Yes, I really do.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, thank you.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Does it help because you look 25?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "MITH: I don't know.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "What's the thing you'd be proudest of, do you think?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Well, to be honest with you, man, that's really not what I am, you know.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "But why have you become such a popular adviser, guru, relationship adviser?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, it's not what is being put out there today in our music and our videos.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What are the principles of manhood?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Well, it was set up to be wider than that, but because I promote it on my radio show, 97 to 98 percent of the kids that end up at the program are African-American.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "ORGAN: Is your mentoring program aimed primarily at young black men or is it wider than that?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I mean, absolutely.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "And if so, what is it?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "He taught me hard work.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "What values did he give you?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Well, I think my father would be proud of me right now, you know.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "What would he have made of what you have made of yourself?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "You know, I think a couple relationships he would have wanted me to get it together a little sooner, because my mother and father was married for 64 years.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "What would he have scolded you for?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "It's kind of OK, because what I've learned about mistakes and failures is that they're not just complete wipeouts.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "What would you say to yourself?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I know that you didn't want to have the bad stuff, but that was a nice line.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "You played that one?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "I don't know that I could because I just think, you know, it was at a bad time for me.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "If you had your time again in that relationship, what would you do differently to try to stop that from happening?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "I mean, exactly, man.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Is that how you see it?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Do you think that you're now married for life?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Definitely.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Do you believe inside you this is it?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "What I have now.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What was it, do you think, you were really look for in a woman?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I have a woman who wakes up who's completely happy with herself.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Which is what?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "You know, could have been worse.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Then why are my husband and my pool man looking for his and his bathroom towels?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, for my take on everything, I think people should find love, whatever that is.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Tell me, in all your kind of studies for these books and things, is your conclusion that interracial relationships, marriages, should be encouraged or not encouraged?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Because, see -- there's nothing in it for you.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "As a member of the male species, why the hell would you tell women what we really mean?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Scented candles?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "You.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Reading about love and relationships?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110617pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 674}]